

Pavlo Avramenko

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Q Lisboa, Portugal

✓ pauloavra@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/paulo-avramenko/

github.com/avrapaulo

my-journey.pauloavra.vercel.app/

KEY SKILLS

Programming Languages:

JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, SASS, C#

Frameworks/Libraries:

React, Next.js, Jest, Redux, Tailwindcss, Node.js, Framer Motion, WebPack, Jest, Lint, Prettier

Tools:

Git, Yarn, NPM, VSCode

Agile & Lean:

Scrum, Kanban

CI/CD:

Jenkins, CircleCI

LANGUAGES

Portuguese (Native) Russian (Native) English (Fluent)

Summary

I've been developing and working since 2016. I am very proud of my career paths, though I believe the best is yet to come. Raising my standards for new challenges, I aspire to grow as a developer continuously learning more about the latest technologies and developments that are coming out of the tech ecosystem. I believe in a combination of humbleness, passion, dedication, hard work, and fun for a successful path.

Work Experience

Software Engineer

03/2020-Present

Moteefe

Lisbon, Portugal

In my first team, we had the mission to increase the conversion rate of the platform and provide the best checkout experience to the user. Later, I decided to switch to a new team that was being created at the time, whose goal was to remove the front-end code from the back-end monolith Ruby on Rails to Next.js.

Software Engineer

08/2019-03/2020

Talkdesk

Lisbon, Portugal

Create responsive, maintainable, and scalable applications via React, Redux to guarantee a topnotch and consistent UX. To be used by users of the main application as an installable extension to improve user experience and satisfaction.

Consultant

08/2018-08/2019

Hitachi Consulting

Lisbon, Portugal

Create the best user experience to attract foreign customers to the Outlet Villages owned by the client. Main responsibility Improve and maintain different microservices, Give support to the client team in the UK.

Full-Stack Software Engineer

07/2017-08/2018

PROEF IT

Lisbon, Portugal

Design and implement a single page application on top of RESTful API as a healthcare startup web app (Promptly). Communicate with the customer

Full-Stack Software Engineer

01/2016-07/2017

Beyond NewsGen

Lisbon, Portugal

Rebranding O'Jogo and JN. Maintain and improve client main sites DN, TSF, O'Jogo, and JN. Regular syncs with the client.

Education

ISTEC UNIVERSITY

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science, 2015 - 2018

